Guide to the Ladyslipper, Inc. Records, 1965-2011 and undated RL.10140
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Financial Series, 1975-2007; 1
  - Vendor Files subseries, 1976-2007; 1.2
    - Moving on Music, 1981-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Ms. Classifieds, 1982-1987; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Musica Mundi, 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Musicrama Record & Tape, 1985-1993; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Muzima Music, 1982-1992; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - MVO Records, 1989-1992; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - MY Publichsing, 1982; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - National Association for the Exchange of Industrial Resources (3 folders), 1985-1993; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Nancy Scott/Reminiscent Records, 1989-1992; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Nancy Tucker, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Nancy Vogl, 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Natural Source, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Nashville Custom Productions, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Nelson-Hall Inc., 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Neutral Records, 1982-1985; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - New Age Journal, 1990-1994; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - The New Music Times, 1977-1979; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - New Radio & Performing Arts, Inc., 1985; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - New Woman Press, 1980; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Night Heron, 1983; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Night Rainbow, 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Nashville Record Productions, Inc., 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Nuages Records, 1983-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Off Centaur Publications, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - On Our Way Productions, 1984-1989; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - On Tour Publications, 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Open Door Records, 1976-1987; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Original Cast Records, 1982-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Outlaw Women, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Out & Out Books, 1978-1980; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Out From Under Tapes, 1978-1983; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Ozark Cener of Language Studies, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Paid My Dues, 1980; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Palo Alto Records, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Pauline Moore, 1984-1987; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Peaceful Women, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Peerless Plastic Molding, Inc. (2 folders), 1980-1981 (Box 20)
    - Peters International, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Phase 2, 1981-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Pickwick Distribution Companies, 1980-1983; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Plymouth Mills, Inc., 1978-1983; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Pomegranate Rose, 1987-1993; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Pratiti Music, 1983-1987; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Premier Electronics Lab, 1983-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Progressive Records, 1981-1984; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Propinquity Management, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Quick Fox, 1981; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - The Radish Zone, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Rand Industries, 1993; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Red, 1993; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - R&J Records, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Rattlesnake Annie, 1981; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Razzberry, 1983; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Rebecca Records, 1983-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Re-Bop Records, 1990-1993; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Red Beans Records, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Redouble Records, 1980; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Revolutions, 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Revonah Records, 1978-1984; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Rising Records, 1983; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Ross-Ellis LTd., 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Ruffled Feathers Music, 1982-1986; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Ruth Pelham, 1985; 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Ruth Rocchio, 1 folders (Box 20)
    - Salamander, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sally Rogers, 1985; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Schneewittchen, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sea Wave Records, 1977-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - SheLan Records, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sierra/Briar Records, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sight & Sound, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Snap Dragon, 1984; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Software, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Solid Ground, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sonic Prisms, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sonyatone Records, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Soundless Sound, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Spoken Arts, 1979-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Star Dry Goods Co, 1982-1985; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Starfire Productions, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Carol Steinel, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Susan Strauss, 1986-1989; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Stroppy Cow Records, 1980-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Submaureen Records, 1976-1980; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sugar Hill Records, 1987-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sumaje Tapes, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Sweetwater Caterers, 1982; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Synergy Records, 1981-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - The Talman Company, Inc., 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Teddy Bear Records, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Terrapin Records, 1979-1982; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Tete's Noires, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Three Fathom Productions, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Thrival Productions, 1990-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Thrushwood Records, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Ticket Craft, 1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - The Touch/Helen Jessup, 1985; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - A Traveling Jewish Theatre, 1988-1994; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Treelight Productions, 1988-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Trotter Records, 1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Troubadisc, 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Twin Cities Records, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - TwinTide, 1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Two in Twenty, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - U-Haul, 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Vicker, 1980; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Voyager Recordings and Publications (2 folders), 1978; 1990-1994 (Box 21)
    - Video-SIG, 1987-1990; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Vychodna Dolina, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Women Library Workers, 1982; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Women's Music Express, 1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Wakarusa Records, 1981-1984; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Warner Brothers, 1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Washington Sisters, 1985-1987; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Waterhouse Records, 1980-1984; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Wear-Guard, 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Whatever Publishing, 1987; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Windsong, 1983-1985; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Wingbow Press, 1987-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Wise Women Enterprises, 1976-1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Wizard Records, 1984; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Womonfolk and Jazz, 1987-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Womanlife Production, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Woman of Power, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Womansong Publishing, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Women's Alliance/Susan Zerner, 1992; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - The Women Composers Calendar, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Women in Music/Chicago, 1980; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - The Women's Music Calendar, 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Wordworks, 1979-1983; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Wormwood Productions, 1983-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Yahoo Records, 1980; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Yellow Orchid, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Zamoiski Co, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - Zephyr Press, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 21)
    - 32 Records, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - 404 Music Group, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Aboveground, 1979-2000; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Abyss Distribution, 1993; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Access Music (2 folders), 1995-2004 (Box 22)
    - Accession, Inc., 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - A.C.E., 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Acoustic Medicine Productions, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Acronym Music, 1995-2002; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Ada Khoury/Pterodactyl Records, 1991-1996; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Alternative Distribution Alliance, 1999; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Adult Children of Heterosexuals, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Alliance Entertainment Corp., 1995; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Aeolus Music, 1989-2002; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Affirmations, 1987-1998; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Ageless Music Works, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Ahowl Productions, 2002-2003; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Aine Minogue, 2003; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - A Gentle Wind, 1982-2001; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Fairewood Studios, 2000-2003; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Alcazar Productions, 1991-2003; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Allegro Corporation, 1993-2003; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - The All Girl Boys/Carolyn Cirimele, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Alligator, 1994-2003; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Almighty Records (2 folders), 1995-2003 (Box 22)
    - Alula Records, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 22)
    - Amazon Bookstore, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Amber Lotus Publishing, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Amy Ford, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Amy Sophia Marashinsky, 1991-1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - American Helix, 1986-1996; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Amy Williams/Tri-Muse Records, 1997-2000; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Angela Motter, 1992-2003; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Anique Lamerduc, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Anna Crusis Women's Choir, 1993-2003; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Anne Seale, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Ann Mortifee, 1991-1996; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Antone's Records, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Apsis Music, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Arhoolie Records, 1979-2002; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - ARTic Siren, 1994-1999; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Asiba Tupahache/Spirit of January, 1990-1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Aural Gratification, 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Australian Music International, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Ave Maria Press, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Aym Kano, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Azalea Typography, 1987-1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Azucar Y Crema/Remy Rodriguez, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Azure Records, 1997-2000; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - B&W Music, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - BA Music, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Debbie Diedrich/Babes with Axes, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Baby Boom Music, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - B.A.L.M. Records, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Barbara Hammer, 1987-1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Barb Moreno, 1999; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Barb Yoder/Crone's Throw, 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Goingbarefoot.com, 2000; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Barnes, 1999-2003; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Bay Area Women's Philharmonic, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - BCN/Beacon Records, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Bear & Company Publishing, 1991-2000; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Bear Tribe Publishing, 1990-1996; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - BeJae Fleming, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Belle Curve Records, Inc., 2000-2003; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Bent Records, 1982-1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Beth Holmgren/Malaika, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - The Man from B.E.T.T.Y. Records, 1989-2002; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Betty Dodson, 1986-2001; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Black Socks, 1990-1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - The Blessing Tree, 1989-1996; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Blue Jackel, 1997; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Blue Plate Music, Inc., 1996-2004; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - Blue Wolf Music, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 23)
    - BMG (2 folders), 2001-2005 (Box 24)
    - Bobbi Carmitchell, 1989-1995; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Bons Ritmos/Andy Potter, 1990-1996; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Boston Gay Men's Chorus, 1995-2003; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Carolyn Brandy, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Brave Ann Music, 1989-1996; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Brooke Medicine Eagle, 1987-2004; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Caf? Noir, 1988-1993; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Calabash Productions, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Caroline Aiken, 1993-2004; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - C1TV, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Cambria, 1980-1996; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Can Too Records, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Canyon Records, 1984-2002; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Circle of Aradia, 1988-1997; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Rainbow Women Production, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Carolyn Gage, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Carondelet Productions, 1993-2001; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Caryn Lin/Fast Forward Productions, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Cat B'Lues, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Cathy Miller, 1987-1995; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Cathy Palmer, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Catie Curtis, 1992-2005; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Nicki Scully, 1987-1998; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - CC Studios, 1985-1997; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - CD One Stop, 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Cedco Publishing Company, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Ceili's Muse, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Celestial Harmonies (2 folders), 1991-2001 (Box 24)
    - Centaur Entertainment, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Charles Cermele, 2002; 1 folders (Box 24)
    - Changing Woman, 1992-2004; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Chacra Music U.S.A., 2002-2004; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Charis Video, 1988-1996; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Charlie Pacheo, 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Cherrywood Station, 1992-1997; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Chiswick Packaging Products, 1991-1997; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Christa Resources, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Church of Religious Science, 1995-1999; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Cheryl Melody Productions, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Cindy Kallet/Stone's Throw, 1990-2003; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Cindy Paley Aboody, 1990-2001; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Circle, 1984-1998; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - City Spark Records, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - City Hall Records, 1999-2005; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Claudia Queen/Womonsounds, 1986-1995; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Christine Lavin Music, 1998-2004; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Clear Light Studios/Deb Criss, 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Clishmaclaver/Jennifer Culley, 1989-1996; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Cloud 9 Music/Barbara Borden, 1989-2002; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Community Music, 1992-2995; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Compass Rose Music, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Connemara/Siren Song, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Single Pigeon Productions, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Cowboy Girl, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Cowboy Envy, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Coyote Entertainment, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Coyote Oldman, 1989-1996; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Compass Records, 1999-2003; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Creative Muse Productions, 1998-2003; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Caroline Distribution, 1992-2004; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Crossing Press, 1984-1998; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Crow Johnson/Zassafras Records, 1997; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Dixie Chicks/Crystal Clear Sound, 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Culburnie Records, 1994-2004; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Culmination Music/John Orlando, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Diana M. Grove, 1991-1997; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Dandelion Wine Book Co., 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Danika Music, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Dargason Music, 1992-2003; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - Darthe Jennings, 1999-2003; 1 folders (Box 25)
    - David Brown, 1997-2003; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - David Clement, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - David Sereda, 1995-2004; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dargason Music, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dancing Crane Music, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - DCC Compact Classics, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Deb Tiemens/WRT Music Productions, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Debra Riggin Waugh, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Deepspace Disc, 1997-2004; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - The Del Rubio Triplets, 1993-2004; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Cathy Carfagna/The Jazzabels, 1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Reverend Delores Berry, 1999-2004; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Denver Women's Chorus, 1996-2004; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Derivative Duo, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Diana Bitting/Destiny, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Deuce, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Diablo Musica, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dancing Hands Music, 1994-2004; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Diana Earthmission, 1986-2003; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Diana Jones, 1998; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - DiverseCity Records, 1998-2003; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Melinda Di Maio/Adamant Eve, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dink Records, 1996-2003; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Direct Cinema Limited, 1992-2005; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dirty Linen Ltd., 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Discovery Music, 1986-1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dive Deep Productions, 2000-2003; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Decline to Sign Campaign, 1996; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Distribution North America, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Landfill Records, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dolphin Song, 1989-1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dominique Starosta, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Donna B./Black Fire Records, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dos Fallopia, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Double Arrow Record, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Bantam Doubleday Dell Publishing Group, 1993-2000; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dove Paloma Music, 1994-2000; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dove Audio, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - DRG Records, 1985-1998; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dudley Saunders, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - The Del Rubio Triplets, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Desert Voices, 1999-2003; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Drake Entertainment, 2002; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Dyke-Appella, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Earthspirit Community (2 folders), 1993-2001 (Box 26)
    - Earth Magic Productions, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - EarthBeat!, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Earth Dance, 1994-2002; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Earth Mother Productions, Inc., 1999-2005; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Earthtree Music, 1990-1996; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Earth Thunder Productions, 1996-2004; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - E.D. Laningham, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Eighth Note Records, 2000; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Eileen Edmonds, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Electric Love Productions, 1992-1997; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Ellen Seeling, 1997; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Elliot Pilshaw, 1991-1996; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Ember Swift, 2004; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Emily Rose, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Emphatic Records, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Enlightenment, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - The Angels of Venice, 1995; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Eric Lane Barnes, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Erica Wheeler, 1990-1999; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Erin Jacobsen, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 26)
    - Earth Sea Records, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Essence of Magick, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Esther Records, 1989-2001; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Etherean Music, 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - E. Thomas, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Pooky Looky Records, 2000-2004; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Everything Possible, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Everywoman's Books, 1996; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Facets Multimedia, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Fallopian Tubes (2 folders), 1997-2000 (Box 27)
    - Videos.com, 1998; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Feather Boa Records, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Feminazis, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Femme M'Amie, 1994-1999; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Michael Ferreri, 2000-2003; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Fine Tuning Music, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - First Coast Music, 1995-2004; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Firebird Arts & Music, 1997; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - First Light Music, 2001-2003; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - First Run Features, 1990-2004; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Flat Rock Records, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Fluke, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Flowinglass Music, 1997-2003; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Flying Fish, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Folk Era, 1996; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Folk-Legacy, 1983-1996; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Foosh Productions, 1988-1995; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Four Winds Circle, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Four The Moment, 1988-1997; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Four Directions Prodution Company, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Four Winds Trading Company, 1998-2003; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Francine Allen, 1997-2003; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Frankie and Zoe's Printing Palace, 1994-1999; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Frank Rogala, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Freckle Records, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Freeana, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Free the Children, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Friedman Publishing Group, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Full Frame Productions, 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Full Womoon Productions, 1987-1995; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Fusion Distribution, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gadfly Records Inc., 1995-2003; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gaia's Heart, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Grale Company, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gasparo Records, Inc., 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - The Gate Media Group, 2001-2003; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gayweb, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gaywired.com, 1996; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - G.B. Records, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - The Great Body Escape, 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gay Community Social Services of Seattle, 2000-2004; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gean Harwood, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gemm, 1999; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gerri Gribi, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Gifthorse, 2001-2004`; 1 folders (Box 27)
    - Goddess Records (Kennebunkport, ME), 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Goddess Records (Beverly Hills, CA), 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Girls in the Nose, 1994-2004; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Second Coming Records, 2001; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Giuseppe Joe Records, 1997-2003; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Girl Zone, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Gaulkberry Productions, 2001-2003; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Global Pacific, 1984-2002; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Global Beat Media Corporation, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Gay Men's Chorus of LA, 1992-2003; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington (DC), 1994-2003; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - GNP-Crescendo, 1982-2003; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Golden Bough, 1992-2005; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Gold Moon Productions, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Gourd Music, 1991-2004; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Great Atlantic & Pacific Music, 1980-1994; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Green Linnet Records (2 folders), 1981-2002 (Box 28)
    - Seasick Sailor Records (Gretchen Phillips), 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Ground Swell Productions, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Wolfe Video, 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Lodestar Productions (Gypsyheart), 1992-1997; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Halcyon/Deborah Hunseder, 1991-2005; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Hallows Records, 1992-1998; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Friends of the Hammer, 1988-1995; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Hanna Tiferet Siegel, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Hands of the Goddess Press, 1994; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Harcourt Brace, 1998-2003; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Harper and Row Publishers, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Harmonia Mundi USA, 1988-2003; 1 folders (Box 28)
    - Harpworld Music Co., 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 29)
    - Hart Rouge, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 29)
    - Harvey Perr, 2006; 1 folders (Box 29)
    - Hasu Patel, 1995-2003; 1 folders (Box 29)
    - Hay House, 1989-1995; 1 folders (Box 29)
    - Hear Music, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 29)